Kheel, Theodore W. Additional Files. 6021/010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- PERC - Bios, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- PERC - Charts (Box 58, Folder 11)
- PERC - Press Releases, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- Cornell/PERC: Conflict Resolution on UN Peacekeeping, 1996-1997 (Box 58, Folder 13)
- ADR Conference PERC/Cornell Institute on Conflict Resolution, 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 14)
- American Mediation Association, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 15)
- PERC Foundation RE: ADR Survey, 1996-1997 (Box 58, Folder 16)
- PERC - Articles Folder 1 (Box 58, Folder 17)
- PERC - Articles, Etc. Folder 2, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 18)
- Profiles - The New York Times, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- The Port Authority of New York and New Jersey Correspondence, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- The Port of Authority of New York and New Jersey Fare Increase, 1973-1980 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Port Authority - Fare Report, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Convention Center, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Convention Center News Clips, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Convention Center - Impact Analysis, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Convention Center - Environmental Analysis, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- West Side Highway Project Env. Impact Statement, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Theodore W. Kheel vs. Village Voice + Allan Wolper, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- New Jersey Joint Transportation + Communication Committee, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Premco, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Public Employee Relations 6083-2 Statements and Reports Folder 1, 1966-1969 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Public Employee Relations Statements + Reports Folder 2 6083-2, 1966-1969 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Public Employee Relations Statements +_Reports (Folder 3) 6083-2, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- NY State Supreme Court Transcript: City of Amsterdam, NY vs. Public Employment Relations Board of NY, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Public Employment Relations Board - Publications, 1967 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Public Employment Relations commission, New Jersey, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Public employer-employee Relations Study Commission, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Lab Reports - Genetically Engineered Food Files Genetically Engineered Foods - Books, Brochures, etc., 1999 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Lab Reports - Genetically Engineered Food Filed Genetically Engineered Foods - Info RE: DuPont, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Lab Reports - Genetically Engineered Food Files Genetically Engineered Foods - articles, 1999-2000 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Lab Reports - Genetically Engineered Food Files Genetically Engineered Foods: Study by Kathleen McAfee, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Lab Reports - Genetically Engineered food Files Genetically Engineered Food Studies, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- Udayan Gupta / Book on Punta Cana, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Sustainable Developments, LLC, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Punta Cana Caribbean biodiversity (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Conference Attendee List, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  July 26 - 30
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Conference Brochures, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Communique Cornell Pubs, 2000-2001 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Punta Cana - misc. Publications Zoning + Plan, 1997-2002 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Punta Cana Formation Agreement w/ Club Med + Club Mediterranean, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Punta Cana Correspondence, 2000-2005 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Punta Cana Correspondence RE: Continental airlines, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory Cornell University Correspondence, 1998-2005 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Punta Cana Biodiversity Laboratory Cornell University Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- New York Times Journalism Institute Punta Cana/NY Times Conference, Flight Arrangements, 2006 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- New York Times Journalism Institute Punta Cana Files, 2006 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- New York Times Journalism Institute Punta Cana Files, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  March 11-18
- New York Times journalism Institute Punta Cara CD Background, 2006 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Punta Cana B.R. Articles/Brochures (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Punta Cana - Info RE Caribbean Basin (Caribbean Central American Action), 1987 (Box 61, Folder 16)
- Punta Cana RE: Cuomo/Donahue Overseas Co. LLC, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 17)
- RE: Punta Cana Yacht Club - RE: American International Underwriters (AIG) AIG Conference: RE Investment in Punta Cana + AGIs Blocked Funds and Central Bank, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 18)
- RE: Punta Cana Yacht Club - RE: American International Underwriters National Union Fire Ins. Co. - Proposed Agreement, 1990- 1991 (Box 61, Folder 19)
- RE: Punta Cana Yacht Club - RE: American International Underwriters (AIG) Investment in Punta Cana - Notes nod (Box 61, Folder 20)
- RE: Punta Cana Yacht Club - RE: American International Underwriters (AIG) AIG: Legal Research re AIGs Investment in Punta Cana + its blocked Funds, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 21)
- RE: Punta Cana Yacht Club - RE: American International Underwriters Investment in Punta Cana - Misc. Info, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 22)
- Punta Cana Yacht Club Stock Info Prospectus, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 23)
- Punta Cana Yacht Club Minutes, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 24)
- Racial Justice, 1967-1968 (Box 61, Folder 25)
- Railroad Dispute Reports to the Presidents, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Railroad Dispute: Arbitration Awards, 1963 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- railroad dispute, 1964-1970 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Railroad Dispute - Wage Structure Payment Comparisons, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Railroad Dispute - Proposals of the Carriers + Organizations, 1960-1966 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Railroad Dispute - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Railroad Dispute - Report to the Presidents, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Railroad Dispute - Report to the President, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  September
- Railroad dispute - Opening Brief for Carriers, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Railroad Dispute - Carriers Affidavits, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- Railroad Dispute - Fact-finding Report by Dept. of Labor, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- comprehensive Statement of Employees Respecting Proposed Modifications of Special mediation Panel Recommendations, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  Aug 25
- Railroad dispute Press Releases, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Railroad dispute - Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- Railroad Disputes - Clippings, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- railroad Dispute - Duplicates + Drafts, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Railroad Dispute - Questions for Interpretation, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  June 25
- Railroad Dispute - Drafts of contract Clauses (articles) + Misc. Papers, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- Railroad Dispute - Drafts of Contract Clauses (Articles) + Misc. Papers, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 19)
- A. Philip Randolph Educational Fund Kenya Art Project, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Rangel, Charles (Rangel Campaign), 2002 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Rauschenberg - U.N. 50 Universal Exhibit (Dialogues of Peace), 1994-1996 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Rauschenberg, Robert General Correspondence, 1993-2003 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Rauschenberg, Robert In the Matter of the Petition of Untitled Press, Inc. for the Remission of 2 Artworks Seized by US Customs Service, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Rauschenberg, Robert Ozone Poster, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Rauschenberg, Robert List of Prints and Posters Donated, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Rauschenberg, Robert RE: New York Observer Article, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Rauschenberg, Robert Robert Rauschenberg Foundation, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Rauschenberg, Robert Profile, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Rauschenberg, Robert RE: Untitled Press - employment Agreement, 1988-1994 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- Rauschenberg, Robert Brochures, etc., 1985-1998 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Rauschenberg, Robert American Visions/Robert Hughes (Box 63, Folder 13)
- Last Turn, Your Turn (Earth Summit, Rio de Janeiro) Correspondence, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 14)
- Last Turn, Your Turn (Earth Summit, Rio de Janeiro Earth Summit Press Release, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Last Turn, your Turn (earth Summit, Rio de Janeiro) Rauschenberg, Robert, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 16)
- Rauschenberg, Robert RE: State Taxes Folder 1, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 17)
- Rauschenberg, Robert RE: State Taxes Folder 2, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 18)
- Rauschenberg, Robert RE: State Taxes Folder 3, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 19)
- Riverdale Senior Services 32nd Anniversary Spring Celebration, 2006 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Rohan, Patrick, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Deposition of Chemical Bank by Susan M. Walker, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Roig: Dep. Of chemical Bank by Charles Lefebure, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Deposition of Patricia J. Meier, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Agreement between Banco Central, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Roig v. Chemical: Commercial Bank Refinancing Proposal and Economic Memorandum, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Pleadings (Folder 1), 1987 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Pleadings Folder 2, 1987-1989 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Correspondence between Commercial Roig + chemical Relating to Loan, 1981-1986 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Extra Copies of Pleadings and Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Agmt. Between Chemical + comercial Roig, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Asigmt. Of Claim, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 14)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Promissory Note and Tax Exempt Letter, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 15)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical CMB Documents (Chase Manhattan Bank), 1981 (Box 64, Folder 16)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Borrowing Documents, 1981-1986 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Legal Research, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Documents Produced Folder 1, 1980-1986 (Box 64, Folder 19)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Documents Produced Folder 2, 1980-1986 (Box 64, Folder 20)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Documents Produced Folder 3, 1980-1985 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Documents Produced Folder 4, 1980-1986 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Documents Produced Folder 5, 1983-1986 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Documents Produced Folder 6, 1984-1986 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Documents Produced (folder 7), 1984-1986 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Guillermo Roig v. Chemical Documents Produced Folder 8 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Rinck v. Smith - smith + Davis - Smith, timothy (Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Schmidt, Robert Individual Investor, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Sen, amartya, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Sheeky, Gail, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Smith, David (Miscellaneous) (Federated, Cascade Linen), 1988 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- soft Money Campaign Miscellaneous Folder 1, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Soft Money Campaign Miscellaneous Folder 2, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Soft Money Campaign Folder 3, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Soft Money Campaign Folder 4, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- soft Money Campaign Folder 5, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- soft Money Campaign Folder 6, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Sprecher, Drewel RE: Book on Nuremberg Trial, 1997 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- St. John's University Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Styl - Rite Optics, Inc. Correspondence + memos, 1975-1977 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Styl-Rite Optics, Inc. Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Styl-Ride Optics, Inc. contract, 1975-1976 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Talent Four Artists, Ltd. RE: Movie Corresponce + Memos, 1976-1979 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- talent Four Artists, Ltd. (RE: Movie) Drafts, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- talent Four Artists, Ltd. RE: Movie Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Talent Four Artists Ltd. RE: Movie "The Bill W. Story (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Tarter, Fred RE: The Pharmacy Fund, 1996-1998 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Traffic + Transit, 2007 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Traffic + Transportation Task Force, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Trans World airlines Inc. Charles S. Parks, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Trans World Airlines, Inc. John Roche, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Treesdale, Inc., 1996 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Troncoso, Lorenzo Garcia (Miscellaneous) Re: Relationship w/ the Bank of New York, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Troy, William RE: Cascade (Elec. Generating Plant), 1984-2002 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Troy, William - miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- US Industries, 1974-1976 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- United Transportation Union folder 1 Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 68, Folder 10)
- United Transportation Union folder 2, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 11)
- UTU News Article, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 12)
- Universal Education corp., 1974-1975 (Box 68, Folder 13)
- UV Industries Liquidating Trust Executive Compensation, 1985-1987 (Box 68, Folder 14)
- Vega, Bernardo Misc, 2000 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- vice Pres Summit - 21st Century Skills for 21st Century Jobs, 1997-1999 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Virginia Tech, 2004-2005 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Virginia Tech Lead Initiatives Binder, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Wages - Conference on Industrial Opportunities + Jobs in NYC, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- War Labor Board, 1943 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- West Side Highway, 1974-1975 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Western Union Corporation, 1975-1976 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Western Union - Director's Agreement, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- New Valley Corp. (formerly Western Union), 1996 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Wilson, Steve RE: King World Contract, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- workforce distance Learning Foundation (Formerly Labor + Mgmt. Distance Learning Fdn.) Fact Sheet, Agenda, Workplace Learning Outlines, 2000 (Box 69, Folder 12)
- Workforce Learning Services, LLC Correspondence, 2000-2003 (Box 69, Folder 13)
- Workforce Distance Learning Foundation (formerly Labor + Mgmt, Distance Learning Fdn.) Video Conferencing Equipment, 1999- 2002 (Box 69, Folder 14)
- RE: Workforce Learning Services LLC, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 15)
- Labor +_Mgmt. Distance Learning Foundation IRS Info, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 16)
- Labor + Mgmt. Distance Learning Foundation RE: Cisco Systems, Inc., 1999 (Box 69, Folder 17)
- Labor _ Mgmt. Distance Learning Foundation Sales Agreement between World Internet Resources, Inc. + Labor + Mgmt. distance Learning Fdn. (Box 69, Folder 18)
- Labor + Mgmt. Distance Learning Foundation Corporate Records, 1998-1999 (Box 69, Folder 19)
- Labor + Mgmt. Distance Learning Foundation Mission Statement, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 20)
- Labor + Mgmt. Distance Learning Foundation Website Development, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 21)
- Labor + Mgmt. distance Learning Foundation RE: Charles Francis Proposal DCI, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 22)
- Labor + Mgmt. Distance Learning Foundation Articles, 1999-2002 (Box 69, Folder 23)
- Int'l Council on Distance Learning, 1997-1998 (Box 69, Folder 24)
- Int'l Council on Distance Learning IRAA/Distance Learning/ Conflict Res. Website, 1999-2000 (Box 69, Folder 25)
- International Center on Distance Learning for Lifelong Adult Learners, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 26)